wolf-howl.com 2019-12-17

# Online Privacy and Policy – Project Veritas

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Project Veritas collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of [www.projectveritas.com](http://www.projectveritas.com/) (the “website”). This Privacy Policy applies to the website and all products and services offered by Project Veritas.

**Information We Collect Automatically**  
If you visit our website to browse, read, or download information:

  * Your web browser automatically sends us (and we may retain) information such as the: 
    * Internet domain through which you access the Internet (e.g., yourServiceProvider.com if you use a commercial Internet service provider, or yourSchool.edu if you use an Internet account from your school);
    * Internet Protocol address of the computer you are using;
    * type of browser software and operating system you are using;
    * date and time you access our site; and
    * the Internet address of the site from which you linked directly to our site.
  * We will use this information as aggregate data to help us maintain this site, e.g., to determine the number of visitors to different sections of our site, to ensure the site is working properly, and to help us make our site more accessible and useful.
  * We will not use this information to identify individuals, except for site security or law enforcement purposes.
  * We will not obtain personally-identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information.

**Other Information We Collect**  
If you choose to identify yourself (or otherwise provide us with personal information) when you use our online forms or services:

  * We will collect (and may retain) any personally identifying information, such as your name, street address, email address, and phone number, and any other information you provide. We will use this information to try to fulfill your request and may use it to provide you with additional information at a later time. We may share your information with third parties.
  * If you request information, services, or assistance, we may disclose your personal information to those third parties that (in our judgment) are appropriate in order to fulfill your request. If, when you provide us with such information, you specify that you do not want us to disclose the information to third parties, we will honor your request. Note, however, that if you do not provide such information, it may be impossible for us to refer, respond to or fulfill your request.
  * If your communication relates to a law enforcement matter, we may disclose the information to law enforcement agencies that we deem appropriate.

**How Long We Keep Information**  
We may keep information that will collect for an unlimited period of time.  
**Use of Cookies**  
Our website may use “cookies” to enhance your experience. Your web browser places cookies on its hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about it. You may choose to set your web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you do so, note that some parts of the website may not function properly.  
**Google Analytics**  
We use a tool called “Google Analytics” to collect information about use of this site. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this site, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to this site. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve this site. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit this site, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this site, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the [Google Analytics Terms of Use](http://www.google.com/analytics/tos.html) and the [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html). You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this site by [disabling cookies](http://www.usa.gov/optout_instructions.shtml) on your browser.

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), in that we do not knowingly collect or maintain personal information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, information and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years of age or older.

**Your Access to and Control Over Information**  
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time by contacting us via the email address given on our website: [info@projectveritas.com](mailto:info@projectveritas.com).

**Links to Other Websites**  
Our website may contain links to other websites. Any personal information you provide on the linked pages is provided directly to that third party and is subject to that third party’s privacy policy. This Policy does not apply to such linked sites, and we are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of these websites or any other sites that are linked to from our website. We suggest you to learn about their privacy and security practices and policies before providing them with personal information.

**Security**  
We take reasonable precautions to protect your information in an effort to prevent loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.   Please be aware, however, that despite our efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable and no method of data transmission that can be guaranteed against any interception or other type of misuse.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way.  You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information.  The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
Project Veritas has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will inform you and revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage you to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your Acceptance of These Terms**  
By using the website, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our website. Your continued use of the website following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Donations**

PROJECT VERITAS is recognized by the IRS and States as A Legitimate Educational Organization Serving the Public Interest.

PROJECT VERITAS is recognized as a tax exempt organization under section 501(c)(3) of the Internal Revenue Code. Your donations are tax deductible as allowed by federal law and the laws of various states. By donating, you may receive emails from our organization. You may unsubscribe at any time.

California: PV’s audited financial statement is available upon request to PROJECT VERITAS (PV). 100 percent of your gift may be deducted under Federal and State income tax laws. Florida: A COPY OF THE OFFICIAL REGISTRATION AND FINANCIAL INFORMATION MAY BE OBTAINED FROM THE DIVISION OF CONSUMER SERVICES BY CALLING TOLL FREE WITHIN THE STATE, 1-800-435-7352. REGISTRATION DOES NOT IMPLY ENDORSEMENT, APPROVAL, OR RECOMMENDATION BY THE STATE. PV’s registration number is CH15951. Georgia: Upon request, PV will provide a full and fair description of this and its other programs, and a financial statement or summary. Maryland: A copy of PV’s current financial statement is available on request to PROJECT VERITAS, 3213 Duke Street, #625, Alexandria, VA 22314. For the cost of copies and postage, registration documents, and other information are available from the Maryland Secretary of State. Minnesota: 100 percent of your gift may be deducted as a charitable contribution under Federal and state laws. Mississippi: The official registration and financial information of PV may be obtained from the Mississippi Secretary of State’s office by calling 1-888-236-6167. Registration by the Secretary of State does not imply endorsement. New Jersey: INFORMATION FILED WITH THE ATTORNEY GENERAL CONCERNING THIS CHARITABLE SOLICITATION MAY BE OBTAINED FROM THE ATTORNEY GENERAL OF THE STATE OF NEW JERSEY BY CALLING (973) 504-6215. REGISTRATION DOES NOT IMPLY ENDORSEMENT. New York: Upon request, a copy of PV’s last annual report filed with Attorney General is available from PV or from the New York State Attorney General’s Charities Bureau, Attn: FOIL Office, Department of State, 120 Broadway, New York, New York 10271. North Carolina: Financial information about this organization and a copy of its license available from the State Solicitation Licensing Branch at (888) 830-4989. The license is not an endorsement by the state. Pennsylvania: The official registration and financial information of PV may be obtained from the Pennsylvania Department of State by calling toll-free within Pennsylvania, 1-800-732-0999. Registration does not imply endorsement. Virginia: A financial statement is available from the State Division of Consumer Affairs in the Department of Agriculture and Consumer Services upon request. Washington: The registration statement required by the Charitable Solicitation Act is on file with the Secretary of State. Additional information can be obtained by calling 1-800-332-4483. West Virginia: West Virginia residents may obtain a summary of the registration and financial documents from the Secretary of State, State Capital, Charleston, West Virginia 25305. Registration does not imply endorsement.

**Contacting Us**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this website, or your dealings with this website, please contact us at:

**Project Veritas**  

This document was last updated on  **6/29/2018**.
